export let questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "q1-question",
    answers: ["male-only", "male-prefer", "female-only", "female-prefer" ,"general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "q2-question",
    answers: ["costly-only", "costly-prefer", "frugal-only", "frugal-prefer", "general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "q3-question",
    answers: ["damage-prioritize", "tank-prioritize", "support-prioritize","general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "q4-question",
    answers: ["stagger-prioritize", "weakpoint-prioritize", "counter-prioritize","utility-allrounder-prioritize", "general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: "q5-question",
    answers: ["backhead-prioritize", "backhead-prefer", "hitmaster-prioritize", "hitmaster-prefer", "general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "q6-question",
    answers: ["nuke-prioritize", "nuke-prefer", "const-prioritize", "const-prefer", "cycle-allrounder-prioritize", "cycle-allrounder-prefer", "general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "q7-question",
    answers: ["range-midlong-prioritize", "range-midlong-prefer", "range-midshort-prioritize", "range-midshort-prefer", "general-neutral"],
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "q8-question",
    answers: ["q7-answer-prioritize", "q7-answer-prefer", "q7-answer-3", "q7-answer-4"],
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "q9-question",
    answers: ["q8-answer-prioritize", "q8-answer-prefer", "q8-answer-3", "q8-answer-4"],
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "q10-question",
    answers: ["q9-answer-prioritize", "q9-answer-prefer", "q9-answer-3", "q9-answer-4"],
  },
  {
    number: 11,
    question: "q11-question",
    answers: ["q10-answer-prioritize", "q10-answer-prefer", "q10-answer-3", "q10-answer-4"],
  },
    {
    number: 12,
    question: "q12-question",
    answers: ["q11-answer-prioritize", "q11-answer-prefer", "q11-answer-3", "q11-answer-4"],
  }
];
